各位好啊
Hey, gentlemen.
- 嘿  - 你好
- Hey.  - Hello.
如果你们有人
If any of you are looking for
在考虑情人节要干什么 我和Amy将要
something to do on Valentine's Day, Amy and I'll be streaming
首次在线直播"旗乐融融"节目
our first-ever live episode of Fun With Flags.
欢迎你们加入 和我们一起庆祝
You're welcome to join us as we celebrate the timeless
风和布块永恒的爱恋
love affair between wind and flapping fabric.
我和Penny预约了一起吃晚饭
Penny and I have dinner reservations that night,
但其它时候我也不会加入的
but any other time, no.
抱歉 我和Bernie打算试用
Sorry, Bernie and I are breaking in
新的热水浴缸 你们懂的
the new hot tub, if you know what I mean.
不懂 Raj呢?
Not a clue. Raj?
和Emily一起过情人节
Spending Valentine's Day with Emily.
听起来你不是很兴奋啊
You don't sound very excited about it.
我挺兴奋的 大... 大概
Oh, I am, I am. I g... I guess
我还在纠结我和Emily相不相配
I'm still wondering if Emily and I are right for each other.
这和与你一起喝咖啡的妹子有关系吗?
Does this have to do with that girl you had coffee with?
你是指那个我三句不离的强壮性感天使?
You mean the strong, sexy angel I can't stop thinking about?
谁知道呢
Who can say?
你一直都在说要和Emily分手
You've been talking about breaking up with Emily forever.
- 怎么到现在都没付诸行动?  - 对
- Why don't you just do it already?  - Yeah, just
- 早死早超生啊  - 你们
- get it over with.  - Well, you
说起来倒是轻巧
say it like it's easy.
你们有谁
Have any one of you
和别人分过手?
ever broken up with anyone?
- 没有  - 不算有
- No.  - Not really.
好吧 我有次一不小心在滴滴上打了车
You know, uh, once I ordered an Uber by accident.
结果我还是上车出去兜了风
I just got in and went somewhere.
* 宇宙一度又烫又稠密 *
* Our whole universe was in a hot, dense state *
* 140亿年前终于爆了炸... 等着瞧! *
* Then nearly 14 billion years ago expansion started... Wait! *
* 地球开始降温 *
* The Earth began to cool *
* 自养生物来起哄 穴居人发明工具 *
* The autotrophs began to drool, Neanderthals developed tools *
* 我们建长城 * * 我们建金字塔 *
* We built the Wall * * We built the pyramids *
* 数学 自然科学 历史 揭开神秘 *
* Math, Science, History, unraveling the mystery *
* 一切由大爆炸开始 *
* That all started with a big bang *
生活大爆炸 第九季第15集
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/==--
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 酥酥要上天   时间轴: 影子要下地
校对: UUUU在人间
--==圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hdscg.com/==--
翻译: 酱油影 肉肉君 小黄不小黄 舒大卷子 猫呗 李小宝Licht
你真的要和她分手吗?
So, you really gonna break up with her?
我想是的 你有什么建议吗?
Yeah, I think so. Do you have any advice?
我的确和很多汉子分过手
Well, I have broken up with my fair share of guys.
你看我都和Leonard分手过多少次了
I mean, how many times did I break up with Leonard?
第四次之后我就没计数了
I stopped counting at four.
好吧 我建议你去她家和她分手
All right, my advice to you is do it at her place
这样你想走的时候就能走
so you can leave when you need to,
说实话 速战速决
uh, tell the truth, make it quick
准备好纸巾擦眼泪
and be prepared for tears.
我在进去之前一定会先哭一哭的
Oh, I'm gonna do a pre-cry before I go in there.
拧干我体内的水分
Really dry myself out.
她是指Emily
She meant Emily.
不... 其实不是说Emily
No, I... I really didn't.
你真的要跟我分手?
You're seriously breaking up with me?
对
Yeah.
你还觉得情人节前夕
And you thought right before Valentine's Day
是个分手的好时机?
was a good time to do it?
你说得对 我们过几天在谈分手的事
You're right. Let's talk again in a few days.
嘿 Claire 嗨 我是Rajesh
Hey, Claire. Hi. It's... it's Rajesh.
我... 我想问问你情人节有空吗?
I was... I was wondering if you're free for Valentine's Day?
抱歉 我刚和男朋友复合了
Sorry, I just got back with my boyfriend.
但我刚和女朋友分手啊
But I just broke up with my girlfriend.
情人节前夕分手?
Right before Valentine's Day?
你真是个混蛋
What an ass.
请回到我身边 我们注定是一对!
Please take me back. Our love was meant to be!
我要一个人过情人节了
I'm gonna all alone on Valentine's Day.
你说得没错... 有眼泪
Well, you were right... tears.
好了 我们22分钟后就要开始直播了
Okay, and we are live in 22 minutes.
我好紧张 我希望会有人
I'm nervous. I hope people
来看我们直播 毕竟今天是情人节嘛
will be around to watch even though it's Valentine's Day.
那些在网上看旗类知识节目的粉丝?
People who are fans of an Internet show about flags?
相信我 他们肯定没安排
Trust me, they're around.
说起情人节
Oh, and speaking of Valentine's Day,
今晚我没有忘记你
I haven't forgotten about you tonight.
什么意思?
What do you mean?
你和这个节目一样已经成为我生活中
Well, you've become such an integral
必不可少的一部分
part of my life as well as this show,
我认为只有把你的名字放在标题里才合适
I felt it only right to include your name in the title.
哦
Oh.
太棒了
That is so sweet.
所以从现在开始 这个节目的官方名称将会是
So from now on, this program will be officially known as
Sheldon Cooper博士和
Dr.Sheldon Cooper
Amy Farrah Fowler博士
and Dr.Amy Farrah Fowler
所主持的Sheldon Cooper博士的旗乐融融
present Dr. Sheldon' Cooper's Fun With Flags.
挺顺口的
Catchy.
我想检查一下浴缸的温度
I'm gonna check the temp on the tub.
不要弄得太热了
Don't make it too hot.
不好意思 只有"太火辣"这种温度
Sorry, but "too hot"
我才会进去
is the only temperature I come in.
瞧瞧你
Look at that,
把毛全剃了啊
you shaved it all.
不用谢
You're welcome.
有个问题 这是我第一次泡澡
Um, question, this is my first hot tub.
里面是应该有一只到处漂的老鼠吗?
Is it supposed to come with a rat flopping around in it?
呃 真的吗? 快把它弄出来
Ew, really? Get it out.
怎么弄?
How? Uh...
希望我们有漏勺
Wish we had a skimmer.
嗯 你把水龙头关上
Uh, you turn off the jets,
我去厨房拿漏勺
I'll get a strainer from the kitchen.
我不知道怎么关啊
I don't know how to turn off the jets.
太好了 我也不知道漏勺在哪里
Good, I don't know where we keep the strainer.
借过一下
Excuse me.
嗯 有坏消息
Uh, bad news.
前台和我说还有至少一小时才能进去
The maitre'D said it's gonna be at least an hour.
一小时? 疯了吧 我们预定过座位的
An hour? What? That's crazy. We have a reservation.
- 我知道啊  - 那你说什么了?
- I know.  - So what did you say?
谢谢 麻烦你了
Thanks, sorry to bother you.
但是我是用混混的口气说的
But I said it like a badass.
好吧 你就不能
All right, well, can't you, like,
给他悄悄塞点钱或者什么的?
slip him some money or something?
真的吗? 我之前从没这么干过 管用吗?
Really? I've never done that before. Does it work?
你是在问人们喜不喜欢钱是吗?
Do people like money, is that what you're asking?
你个把MC平方(爱因斯坦质能方程)当成说唱歌手的女人
A... a lot of attitude from the woman
脾气还不小啊
who thought MC squared was a rapper.
你觉得在这个全国啪啪节时
Now, is that a smart thing to say on a holiday
说这种东西合适吗?
that's basically national sex night?
不好意思 你很漂亮 我太蠢了
I'm sorry. You're pretty, I'm stupid.
你好 嗯
Hello. Uh,
能查一下Hofstadter的座位吗
just checked again for Hofstadter.
还得一个小时?
Still gonna be an hour?
大概是的
I'm afraid so.
哦 谢谢
Okay. Thanks.
嘿
Hey.
你把这个掉地上了吧?
I think you may have dropped this?
哦
Oh.
有人丢了20块吗?
Did anybody lose a 20?
我丢的
I did.
我搞定了
Oh, I took care of it.
好 我们将在
Okay, we are live
五 四 三秒后开始直播...
in five, four, three...
哦 等等 擦 我已经按下按钮了
Oh, wait. Oh, shoot, I already pushed the button.
没关系 我们已经在直播了
Never mind, we're live.
大家好
Uh, hello
欢迎收看Sheldon Cooper博士
and welcome to a special live edition
和Amy Farrah Fowler博士...
of Dr.Sheldon Cooper...
主持的Sheldon Cooper博士的...
and Dr.Amy Farrah Fowler present...
旗乐融融特别直播版
Dr. Sheldon Cooper's Fun With Flags.
考虑到今晚的这期节目
Consider tonight's episode
是我们送给各位观众的情人节礼物
a Valentine's Day gift for you, our viewers.
这也是我送给你的情人节礼物 对吧?
It's also my gift to you. That was clear, right?
我不会再另外送东西了
'Cause you're not getting anything else.
我们现在是现场直播
Since we're live,
所以你终于可以和我们连线
you'll finally be able to reach out to us
说说你对旗子的想法和问题
with your flag thoughts and flag questions.
先让我回答几个各位经常提的问题
Allow us to answer a few quick ones that we get all the time.
首先 我的确是个博士
Uh, uh, yes, I really am a doctor.
其次 她的确是我女朋友
Uh, yes, she really is my girlfriend.
还有 我就是喜欢眨眼
No, I just blink a lot,
我没有用莫尔斯电码求救
it's not Morse code for "rescue me."
哦 好...
Oh, uh, ok...
有一位观众打进来了
Uh, here's our first call.
你好 欢迎做客旗乐融融
Hello, and welcome to Fun With Flags.
你的问题是什么?
What's your question?
我到底是怎么了?
What is wrong with me?
为什么我总是毁了自己的生活?
Why am I so self-destructive?
Rajesh啊?
Rajesh?
是我
Yes.
每次我过得很好的时候 我都会毁了一切
Whenever things are going well, I always find a way to ruin it.
你们两个人看上去挺快乐的... 你们怎么做到的?
You two look happy... how do you do it?
- 我觉得首先就是要多沟通  - 等等
- I think it starts with good communication.  - Yeah, wait,
这个问题和旗子没关系 下一位
that's not a flag question. Next caller.
我接下来要说的话
I hope you don't think I'm just saying this
不是因为今天是情人节...
because it's Valentine's Day, but...
我好爱你
I love you so much.
我要把这东西放到你浴袍里
I'm gonna put this down your robe.
它一动不动的 但我觉得它还活着
It's not moving, but I think it's still alive.
那你要不要再把它丢到那里面去放几分钟?
Well, should we put it back in there a few minutes?
不要
No.
而且这不是老鼠 是兔子
No, and it's not a rat, it's a rabbit.
我们要救它
We need to save it.
怎么救啊?
Well, how do we do that?
不知道 你用手机查一下
Um, I don't know, look it up on your phone.
我... 我拿条毛巾把它裹起来
I... I'm gonna wrap it in a towel.
呃... "照顾
Um... "taking care
受伤的兔子"
of injured rabbit."
好的
Okay.
确保它又舒服又暖和
Make sure it's comfortable and warm.
它刚刚洗了个热水澡呢 这条肯定满足了
Well, it was just in a hot tub. I'm gonna say "check."
还有呢?
Anything else?
接下来确保它不脱水
To make sure it's not dehydrated,
喂它喝电解质
feed him an electrolyte solution.
如果它没有反应的话
If it's not responding,
用一条温暖的毛巾擦拭它的面部和生殖器
use a warm cloth to wash its face and genitals.
就是这样
Yeah.
这太荒唐了
This is ridiculous.
我要找那个接待员去
You know, I'm gonna go talk to the maitre d'.
你打算说什么呢?
What are you gonna say?
不知道 我... 我和他调情吧
I don't know. I'm... I'm gonna flirt with him.
这样我可能会不高兴
I don't know if I'm comfortable with that.
反正我今天晚上还是要和你上床的
I'm still sleeping with you tonight.
看看能不能给我们争取个靠窗的位子
See if you can get a table by the window.
你好啊 你叫什么名字?
Hi there. What's your name?
- 我叫Glen  - 天啊
- Glen.  - Oh, boy,
今天这里真是太疯狂了 对吧 Glen?
it is crazy in here tonight, huh, Glen?
- 今天是情人节啊  - 是啊 哎
- Well, you know, Valentine's Day.  - Yes. Oh,
你今天晚上加班 你女朋友肯定很不开心吧
bet your girlfriend is super bummed you had to work tonight.
听着 我们已经等了好久了
Anyway, look, we have been waiting a while,
- 我...  - 我
- and I just...  - With all
无意冒犯 夫人 我实在是没办法
due respect, ma'am, there's nothing I can do.
别叫我夫人
You don't have to call me ma'am.
－ 其实  － 你看
－ Okay.  － I mean,
我们差不多都是同龄人
we're basically the same age.
好吧
Okay.
你几岁啊?
How old are you?
我21岁 你几岁啊?
I'm 21. How old are you?
闭嘴 Glen
Just shut up, Glen.
快点 我们离开这里
Come on, let's get out of here.
- 什么? 为什么?  - 因为我很年轻 走吧
- What? Why?  - Because I'm young. Let's go.
Rajesh 分手后
Rajesh, it's perfectly normal
有各种困惑是非常正常的
to have doubts after breaking up with someone.
你真的这么想?
Well, you really think so?
是的 你知道什么是不正常吗?
Yeah, you know what's not normal?
在旗子秀直播中哭诉感情问题
Blubbering about emotions during a flag show.
除非这感情是指对新西兰
Unless that emotion is excitement over New Zealand
改变旗子感到兴奋
changing their flag.
好运 疯狂的新西兰人 为你们加油
Yeah, good luck, you crazy Kiwis, we're rooting for you.
你的朋友很痛苦
Your friend is hurting.
不
No,
Sheldon说得对
Sheldon's right.
Emily也曾说我
Emily did say I always
总是说自己的心情
talk about my feelings too much.
我想
I-I suppose that
那可能是一段感情中的适当关心
could be a legitimate concern in a relationship.
也许甚至是红旗（危险信号）
Uh, perhaps even a-a red flag.
说到红旗
And speaking of red flags,
来看看这面来自前苏联的性感旗子
check out this sexy number from the former Soviet Union.
好极了 好极了
Hubba, hubba.
又有一个听众拨入电话
Oh. Uh, we-we have another caller.
你好 这里是旗乐融融
Hi. You're on Fun with Flags.
你好 我也想说说我有多么孤单
Hello. I want to talk about how lonely I am, too.
Kripke? 是你吗?
Kripke? Is that you?
是的 我一个人坐在这里
Yeah, I'm just sitting here all by myself
在想我会不会找到一个人和我共度此生
wondering if I'll ever find someone to share my life with.
最好是亚洲女性 18到24岁 不要胖的
Preferably Asian, 18-24, no fatties.
拜托 所有的评论和问题
Please, all comments and questions
都应该是和旗子有关的
should be flag-related.
好吧 我下面的杆子和旗子有关吗?
All right. Is my pole flag-related?
我不觉得无关
I don't see why not.
他吃下去了 这是个好迹象
He's eating. That's a good sign.
你要再等一个小时
You're gonna have to wait one hour
才可以再去游泳哦
until you can go swimming again.
- 他实在太萌啦  - 是啊
- He's pretty cute.  - He is.
我们应该给他起个名吗?
Should we... name him?
今天是情人节
It is Valentine's Day.
叫Valentino怎么样?
How about Valentino?
好啊 一个经典的兔子名
Nice. A classic rabbit name.
彼得兔 罗杰兔 Valentino Wolowitz兔
Peter Rabbit, Roger Rabbit. Valentino Wolowitz Rabbit.
看看那胸毛和龅牙
Oh, look at all that chest hair and overbite.
你当然是一个Wolowitz
Of course you're a Wolowitz.
狗崽子! 他咬我!
Son of a bitch! He bit me!
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
不 我不好!
No, I'm not okay!
野生的兔子可能有狂犬病!
Wild rabbits can have rabies!
你为什么要把手指放到他嘴边?
Oh. Well, why did you put your finger near its mouth?
判断失误 很明显啊
Poor judgment, obviously.
- 他这么小 我确定没关系的  - 怎么可能没关系?
- He's so little. I'm sure it's fine.  - How can it be fine?
我刚刚被一只明显反犹太人的野生动物咬了
I just got attacked by a clearly anti-Semitic wild animal.
这不是我们所计划好的 但也没那么糟 对吧?
It's not what we planned, but this isn't so bad, right?
简直好极了
It is freaking amazing.
很高兴你觉得好点了
Well, glad you're feeling better.
我刚刚只是很饿很暴躁
I was just hungry and cranky,
我之前从来没有被人叫过"夫人"
and I've never been called "ma'am" before.
这有什么大不了的吗?
Is that a big deal?
有点 第一次有人叫你"先生"是什么时候?
Kind of. When was the first time someone called you "sir"?
六年级
Sixth grade,
我穿着休闲西装拿着公文包 所以...
but I wore a sport coat and carried a briefcase, so...
你能相信吗 我遇到你的时候22岁?
Can you believe when I met you I was 22?
简直疯了
I mean, it's crazy!
那些时间都去哪儿了?
Where did all that time go?
你看了很多集的单身汉
Mm, you watched The Bachelor a lot.
是的 接着开玩笑吧
Yeah, go ahead and make jokes,
但你都快奔五了
but your thirties are almost over.
才不是呢
No, they're not.
你都过了三十五了
You're closer to 40 than you are 30.
哈哈! 你嫁给了个老男人
Ha, ha! You married an old man.
这样吧
Tell you what.
今晚我们玩点好玩的
Let's do something fun tonight.
这样也年轻不了啊
Won't make us any younger.
虽然不会 但是我们总有一天会老的
Well, maybe not, but some day we actually will be old,
等到那时再想起今晚
and we'll look back on this night
会回忆起许多乐趣
and remember what a good time we had.
好吧 玩什么?
Okay, like what?
我知道 食物大战!
I know. Food fight!
我继续想吧
I'll keep thinking.
我知道你俩都很孤独 但是
Look, I know you both feel bad about being alone, but sometimes
有时候一个人也是乐得自在
the best thing you can do is take a little time for yourself,
尤其是在刚刚分手之后
especially when you just got out of a relationship.
说起分手
Speaking of ending relationships,
当英国的洪都拉斯变成了伯利兹之后
when British Honduras became Belize,
他们设计了一个画着树的新旗帜
they designed a new flag with a tree on it,
我倒是希望在那棵树上吊死
and I would like to hang myself from that tree.
但是 Amy 你和Sheldon分手之后
But, Amy, when you and Sheldon split up,
不就立马开始和别人约会了吗?
didn't you start dating someone right away?
并... 并没有立马啦
Well, I... I wouldn't say right away.
而且她见了三个男人
And actually, it was three different men.
三个男人?
Three different men?!
天了噜 姑娘 你咋不上天呢?
Damn, girl, way to give the milk away?
Kripke好像掉线了哦
Oh, looks like we just lost Kripke.
我还在呢
Actually, I'm still here.
- 还在吗?  - 在滴
- Now?  - Yup.
还在吗?
Now?
Kripke好像掉线了哦
Oh, looks like we just lost Kripke.
和Emily在一起之前 我单身了很久
Before Emily, I was alone for so long.
我不知道... 还能不能再承受那种感觉
I just... I don't know if I can do that again.
我这里有点东西
Well, you know, here is something
说不定能让你高兴起来
that might cheer you up.
马恩岛的旗帜只是个
The flag of the Isle of Man is nothing but three legs
穿着奇怪内裤的三条腿...
sharing a weird pair of underpants, so...
你还以为你有难处呢
you think you got problems.
我有主意了
I have an idea.
也许咱们的观众里
Maybe someone in our audience
有人愿意和Rajesh约会
would be interested in meeting Rajesh.
女士们 我可以担保
Ladies, I can attest
他是一个善良 英俊 聪明...
that he is a kind, handsome, intelligent...
富二代! 别忘了说富二代!
Rich parents! Don't forget, rich parents!
惯坏了的天体物理学家 不仅...
spoiled astrophysicist who not only...
好吧 倒挺快的
Oh. Well, that was quick.
嗨 这里是旗乐融融
Hi. You're on Fun with Flags.
我好像被人掐掉了
Hey, I think I got cut off.
哈喽 Kripke
Hello, Kripke.
我有一个关于旗帜的问题
I have a flag question.
你和几个男人啪过?
How many men did you have sex with?
什么是有趣又充满年轻活力的呢?
Let's see. What's young and fun?
啊 我们可以去跳舞
Uh, we could go dancing.
你真要去跳舞?
Are you actually gonna dance?
- 当然要去  - 是嘛
- Of course.  - Yeah.
没人想看你跳舞
No one wants to see that.
嘿 去海边裸泳怎么样?
Hey, how about skinny dipping at the beach?
算了 我不想老二给鱼啃了
No, I don't need any fish nibbling my business.
红磨坊上映了!
Oh, there's a screening of Moulin Rouge!
我听说观众可以合唱
I heard the crowd sings along and stuff.
听起来不错 几点开始?
That sounds fun. When's it start?
半夜
Midnight.
半夜 真的吗?
Midnight. Really?
就这样 我们去看
You know what? Let's do it.
好的 太棒了!
Okay, great!
等等 票卖完了
Oh, wait. Uh, it's sold out.
- 谢天谢地  - 棒!
- Oh, thank God.  - Yes!
这上面说 兔子带有狂犬病
It says, rabies in rabbits is
几乎是不可能的
highly unlikely.
－ 太棒了  － 哪里棒?
－ Oh, terrific.  － It's not terrific.
几乎不可能不代表不会发生
Lots of highly unlikely things happen.
你也见过我浴袍下的事实了 但你还是嫁给我了
You saw what's under this robe, and you still married me.
如果你实在放心不下
If you're really worried,
我们就带它去兽医那里检查检查 这还差不多
we'll take him to the vet and have him tested. Good.
谢谢 有了有了 可以这样检查!
Thank you. Oh, okay, there is a test!
你所要做的就是...
All they have to do is...
切开他的头检查他的大脑
cut off his head and check his brain.
切开他的头?
Oh, cut off his head?
那是他小鼻子的位置啊
That's where his little nose is.
他没有表现出任何症状
He's not showing any symptoms.
安全起见 我还是去一趟急诊室吧
I guess I'll just go to the emergency room to be safe.
霍霍 你想太多了
Howie, this is just your hypochondria.
不 当我坐在了静音键上
No, when I sat on the mute button
却以为自己聋了的时候 那才是我想太多
and thought I'd gone deaf, that was my hypochondria.
我们换个时间再告诉他我怀孕了吧
We'll find another time to tell him I'm pregnant.
我想表达的是 这是我第一次
I mean, this is the first time
和别人分手啊
I've ever broken up with someone.
我只是... 没有想到会伤得这么深
I just... I didn't realize it was gonna hurt this much.
确实会这样的
It really can.
宝宝受够了
All right.
这个一点都不好玩
Nothing about this is fun.
没人想聊一聊旗帜
No one wants to talk about flags,
人家都已经十分钟没说一个字了
and I haven't spoken in over ten minutes,
所以 享受你们的节目吧
so, enjoy your new show, Internet.
Amy Farrah Flower出品的... 陪伴
Dr. Amy Farrah Flower Present... With.
很抱歉我打扰你们了
I'm sorry for bothering you.
我马上就挂
I'll hang up now.
等等 Rajesh
No, hold on, Rajesh.
你就没有点同情心
You know, you're not being very sympathetic.
你也知道分手是很难的
You know firsthand that breakups are hard.
好嘛
Fine.
如果你坚持我参与这个的话
If you insist on making me a part of this,
没错 我确实知道这有多伤人
yes, I acknowledge how painful they can be.
但是 伤痛也是有积极意义的
However, pain has an evolutionary purpose.
它能从环境中为我们提供信息
It provides information from the environment
告诉我们这样的行为是对我们不利的
that, uh, behavior isn't good for us.
就像我爱上那个脱衣舞娘的时候
Like when I fell in love with that stripper
我还给她买了一辆普锐斯
and bought her a Prius.
我听不下去了
I'm just gonna push all the buttons.
Raj 你现在这么煎熬我表示很心疼
Raj, now, I'm sorry you're suffering.
当初Amy和我分开的时候 我也很痛苦
When Amy and I were broken up, I also suffered.
就算这听上去很惊人
And this may sound surprising,
但我还是开心自己度过了这个难关
but I'm grateful for having gone through it.
真的吗?
Really?
是的
Yes.
我相信现在我们情比金坚
I believe our relationship now is stronger than ever.
我也这么觉得
So do I.
当初... 我们分开的时候
When... when we were apart,
我明白你对我来说有多重要
I learned how important you are to me.
我也认识到
And I realize
当两个人相爱的时候 有时他们...
that when two people are in love, sometimes they...
情人节快乐!
Happy Valentine's Day!
我们年轻又欢乐!
We are young and fun!
我收回之前的说法
I stand corrected.
确实挺有意思的
Fun.
一起庆祝这次直播成功吧
Congratulations on a successful live show.
还有这个有爱的情人节
And a lovely Valentine's Day.
打扫一点都不年轻又欢乐
Cleaning up is not young and fun.
这个可以有 纸屑大战!
It can be. Confetti fight!
不如你歇会儿吧
Maybe you should take a break.
我来收拾就好
I got this.
你知道confetti的单数形式是confetto吗?
Did you know the singular of confetti is "confetto"?
有意思 那什么时候用单数形式呢?
Interesting, and when would you use the singular?
真高兴你问了
I'm glad you asked.
Amy 你鼻子里有一张纸屑
Amy, you have a confetto in your nose.
不 不 不 另一边 好了没了
No, no, no, no. Other side. There you go.